

+94 76 603 9161

shanaka.vitaz.dev

🦪 github.com/shanaka95

fb.me/cruz404

int.ly/Shahaka33

upwork.com/fl/shanakas3

🕕 hackerrank.com/shanaka95

ABOUT ME

I am a highly motivated and result-oriented individual with a track record of success. I have achieved outstanding results, having attained All Island first place and the highest Z-Score of 3.4869 in the A/L Examination 2015, Engineering Technology stream. Subsequently, I obtained a Bachelor of Information and Communication Technology (BICT) Honours Degree with Second Class Upper Division (3.46 GPA, 4 Years, 120 Credits) from the Faculty of Technology, University of Sri Jayewardenepura. I am currently employed as a Fullstack Web Developer and possess 3+ years of experience in this field. I am confident that I can bring value and make an impact in any organization I work for.

SKILLS & GOALS

Development skills

Front End Web development (Angular)
Backend Web Development (Django, Laravel, Slim)
Database (MySQL, PostgreSQL, Sqlite, Firebase)
Hybrid Mobile App Development (Flutter, Ionic3)
Desktop Application Development (Python + QT)
Chat Bot Development (RASA)
Web Scraping and Automations with Python
Image Processing (Python + OpenCV)

Leadership skills

Former President - USJ FOSS Community
Founder Member - J'pura TechTalks
Founder Member - CodeChamps Online Hackathon
President - ICT Societ of St.Thomas College (2014-2015)
Secretary - Media Unit St.Thomas College (2014-2015)

Goals

My goal is to acquire the necessary skills and experience to become a successful Software Architect.

PROFESIONAL SKILLS

| PYTHON | |
|------------|--|
| JAVASCRIPT | |
| ANGULAR | |
| PHP | |
| MYSQL | |

PERSONAL DETAILS

Full Name Samarakoon Mudiyansela Adikaramlage Walawwe Shanaka Anuradha Samarakoon Name with Initials S.M.A.W.S.A.Samarakoon Address Infront Of School, Maningamuwa, Pallepola, Matale. Date of Birth 24-03-1995 Gender Male Marital Status Single Nationality Sri Lankan

EDUCATION

Nic No.

| | GCE Ordinary Level Examination / | 2011 |
|----|--|------|
| +) | GCE Ordinary Level Examination / St.Thomas College Matale | |

950840080v

| 9 | |
|--|---|
| Sinhala | Α |
| Buddhism | Α |
| Mathematics | Α |
| Science | Α |
| English | Α |
| Citizen Studies | Α |
| History | Α |
| Information and Communication Technology | В |
| Sinhala Literature | С |

+ GCE Advanced Level Examination / 2015 St.Thomas College Matale

| Engineering Technology | А |
|--|--------|
| Science For Technology | Α |
| Information and Communication Technology | / A |
| General English | В |
| District Rank | 01 |
| Island Rank | 01 |
| 7-Score | 3.4869 |

Bachelor of Information and Communication Technology (Honours) - Second Class Upper

Faculty of Technology

University of Sri Jayewadenepura

Bachelor's degree in Information and Communication Technology at the Faculty of Technology, University of Sri Jayewardenepura, Gangodavila, Nugegoda.

GPA - 3.46 / 4.0

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Trainee Software Engineer - CodeGen Intl (Pvt) Ltd

Kriyo Project. May 2020 - Sept 2020

Lecturer (Visiting)

Faculty of Computing - Sri Lanka Institute of Information Technology, Kandy Center. Feb 2022 - Oct 2022

Top Rated Fullstack Developer - Upwork

More than 10 Successfull Projects. 2019 Dec - Present

Fullstack Developer - NAZ360 Technologies

Worked as a Freelancer - 2020 Oct - 2022 Jan

Fullstack Developer - Apudos Ltd

Working as a Freelancer - 2022 Aug - Present

PROJECTS

CodeGen Intl (Pvt) Ltd - SriLanka

Kriyo Project

Employee Feedback and Rating Management System

Angular 10, Spring boot, MySQL, Docker, Apache Tomcat, GitLab,

Jira, REST

NAZ360 Technologies - USA

AbrioTools - Healthcare ERP System

AbrioLiving - Healthcare ERP System

Real Estate ERP System

Software Architecture Design, Memcached, Angular 12, Angular JS, PHP Laravel, PHP Slim, HTML, CSS, SCSS, Bootstrap, MDB Angular, MySQL, Docker, Apache2, Twilio, Google Cloud, AWS, Linux, Jira, Kanban Boards, Bitbucket, REST

Apudos Ltd - UK

Apudos Concierge - Parcel Delivery Management System Apudos Wordpress Website

PHP Zend, Javascript, jQuery, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, MySQL, Apache2, AWS, Linux, Trello, Kanban Boards, Bitbucket

Eggion - Australia

High School Exam Revision Organizing System

Angular 11, RxJS, HTML, CSS, SCSS, Angular Material, MySQL,

Azure DevOps

SA Partners - Canada

Real Estate ERP System

Angular 8, Firebase, Javascript, jQuery, HTML, CSS, MySQL, Github

OnlineClz - Sri Lanka

Tution Class Management System

Python Django, Angular 10, Docker, AWS, HTML, CSS, SCSS, Bootstrap, MySQL, Github, Apache2,

Freelancing Projects - Upwork/Freelancer/Fiverr

CryptoMau Telegram Bot

APK Activator - Web based APK Reverse Engineering App

eyeRescue - Computer Vision Application

LindroidBot - Facebook Messenger Chatbot

Linkedin Scraper (GUI)

Instagram Automation Bot

Salesforce Scraper

Cloudtango Scraper

Email And Telephone number Scraper

Stackoverflow Scraper

SAS eFinance - Financial ERP System

SASTD - Torrents to Google Drive Downloader

Faculty of Technology Android App

Vitaz Event Manager Android App

OTPMaster Android App

Automated Robot Arm with Computer Vision

Maze Solving Robot (Micro Mouse)

Python Django, PHP Laravel, Angular 8,10,12,13, OpenCV, Tensorflow, Telegram API, APKTool, Flutter, Ionic3, RASA, Dialogflow, Facebook Messenger API, Selenium, PyQT, Google Colab, Socket.io, WebSockets, Arduino, RaspberryPI, Linux, Firebase, Javascript, jQuery, HTML, CSS, MySQL, Github, Github Actions, Travis CI, Digital Ocean Cloud

PARTICIPATIONS

Infotel 2018 Innovation Pavilion

Participated in Infotel 2018 innovation pavilion. (EyeRescue project).

HackX 2018 Hackathon

Participated in HackX 2018 hackathon organized by University of Kelaniya.

RealHack Hackathon 2018

Participated in RealHack Hackathon 2018 Organized by University of Kelaniya.

Participated in IESL TechnoHack 2017

CyberFest 2018 CTF Hackathon

Participated in CyberFest 2018 CTF Hackathon organized by NIBM.

Mobitel NB-IoT 2018 Hackathon

Participated in Mobitel NB-IoT 2018 hackathon.

iFest Conference

Participated in iFest Conference organized by UCSC.

PARTICIPATIONS

Mozilla Global Sprint 2018

Participated in Mozilla Global Sprint 2018 organized by WSO2.

Participated in Cyber Security Summit 2018

Participated in CERT CSW Quiz 2019

RoboFest 2018

Participated in Robofest 2018 organized by SLIIT

CodeFest 2019

Participated in Codefest 2019 in "Hack me if you can" CTF organized by SLIIT

Exhibitions at leading Public Schools

Participated in ICT related Exhibitions as a member of Faculty of Technology Team.

"Boost Your business with Facebook" Workshop

Participated in "Boost Your business with Facebook" workshop organized by Facebook.

VOLUNTEERING

DevFest 2019 (GDG SriLanka)

Volunteered in DevFest SriLanka 2019 as a Technical Volunteer - PhotoBooth Application

Disrupt Asia 2019

Volunteered in Disrupt Asia 2019

HOBBIES & INTERESTS

- + Blogging
- + Data Mining and Automations
- (+) Cryptocurrency Investments
- + Computer Games

RESEARCH INTERESTS

- (+) Blockchain Technology & Cryptocurrencies
- + Distributed Computing
- + Cyber Security
- + Cloud Computing
- (+) Web 3.0

RESEARCH EXPERIENCE

Undergraduate Thesis

Generate multi-instrumental progressions for given melodies using Generative Adversarial Networks(GAN)

Research Papers

Bypassing Content-based internet packages with an SSL/TLS Tunnel, SNI Spoofing, and DNS spoofing arXiv preprint arXiv:2212.05447, 2022

NON-RELATED REFEREES

Mr. Garrick Brooks

Owner/Project Manager - NAZ360 Technologies 4430 East Hollygreen Rd Flagstaff, AZ 86004 +1 928-637-6001 gtb@naz360.com

Dr. Senaka Amarakeerthi

PhD (Aizu, Japan)
Senior Lecturer (Grade 1),
University of Sri Jayewardenepura,
+94 71 204 3212
senaka@sjp.ac.lk

Ms. Himanshi Liyanage

Ph.D.(reading) in Computer Science (University of Warsaw), Assistant Professor, University of Lodz, Poland +48 45 258 27 45 himanshi@sjp.ac.lk

CONSENT

I hereby declare that all above-mentioned information is in accordance with fact or truth up to my knowledge and I bear the responsibilities for the correctness of the above mentioned particulars.

28th December, 2022 Date <u> Lak</u>

Signature